evolutionwow.org 2011-10-04

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

Please take a moment to review these rules and policies detailed below. If you agree with them, then you may proceed with entering the website.

**User Submitted Data**

Any and all data you enter into this website becomes property of the owners of this site. Because of the community nature of this site, any and all information you submit should be considered publicly viewable - present and future. Submissions include any and all information you type into any field within this website (with the exception of any passwords and personal information).

**Cookies**

We use cookies as part of the login process and throughout the entire site to uniquely identify members and their accounts. We may deliver third party advertisements that may or may not use their own cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies for our site only and does not cover the use of cookies by third party advertisers. ****

**Email Addresses**

We will not give out or sell your email address to third parties. We will only contact you through the provided email address with important news about site related issues or for matters directly related to your account. ****

**Contests and Promotions**

Any information you submit when entering a contest will only be used to facilitate your contest entry. We will seek your permission if such data will be used in any other ways. ****

**Extenuating Circumstances**

In some instances such as legal action and the enforcement of website Terms of Service and Rules, we may be required to reference and use information provided and/or gleaned as a result of your interactions with our website or associated sites. ****

**Server Logs and Statistics**

Like the vast majority of websites, we collect server log information such as IP address, browser type, operating system etc. We refer to this information on aggregate (no personally identifiable information) and use it for internal website optimization purposes and to validate traffic claims with potential advertisers. ****

**Change of Ownership**

In the case that our site goes through a change in operations such as a merger, acquisition, partial exchange of assets and/or funds and such actions significantly affect this privacy statement, you will be given 15 days notice to re-accept or decline such changes in regards to your future relationship with us. ****

**Links**

Our site contains links to 3rd party websites that do not follow this privacy policy. ****

**Notification of Changes**

We reserve the right to change, edit, modify, submit or retract the privacy policy at any time and without notice. However, we may choose to notify website users of changes to the website through the homepage or within the forums. ****

**Legal Requirements**

We may be required to turn over your information when deemed necessary by law. ****

**Liability**

The Privacy Policy documents our guidelines in regards to treating personal information. However, it does not guarantee these standards will always be met. Factors beyond our control may require one or more of the guidelines outlined above to be edited, altered, modified and/or be treated on a case-by-case basis at any time and without notice. All alterations to the Privacy Policy will be retroactive to first contact with this website. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties relating to the upkeep and enforcement of this Privacy Policy.
